Hi, my name is Georgia Crone, I am the founder of the ethical calm community
and in this
video I'm hopefully going to answer any questions you may have and explain how
it all works.
For my own personal experience when I first started webcom and when I was 18 I
know how
daunting it can be. This is why I created a community with that in mind. I
wanted to
create a safe space for women, a place where they feel comfortable to begin and
thrive
on their new webcam journey. Starting a company with ethics at its core, it was
very important
to me. I wanted to create a community where women feel protected and empowered.
I wanted
to create a completely open and honest community where the women feel listened
to and supported.
This is why I created the ethical calm community. We are committed to sticking
to our core values
and code of ethics. Webcaming can be a very lucrative industry when executed
correctly.
Not only can you make a lot of money from the comfort of your own home, you do
this while
setting your own working schedule, your own hours and your own boundaries. We
are here
to advise you, but we would never tell you that you need to be on webcam for
X amount
of time. You are completely your own boss. The main reason why I started webc
aming was
because I wanted to feel free and take my life back. Freedom to me back then
was making
money on my own schedule so I had time to spend with my friends and family. So
that's
exactly what I did. Now freedom to me is travel. Webcam has allowed me to
travel the world
and live in Spain, Amsterdam and Thailand. All you need is your laptop and the
motivation
to succeed. There aren't many jobs like this and I would be forever grateful I
got into
this line of work and trust me you will too. I've personally seen hundreds of
success stories
from women of all ages who longed for the change. I've seen women quit their
nine to
five and completely tear their life around with the help of webcam. But I've
also seen
women who stay at their jobs and webcam every now and again just to bump up
their monthly
wages as well as students who webcam to support themselves while they're
studying. This is
the beauty about webcam if it's around your lifestyle. So you're probably
wondering how
it all works and how you get started. Once you leave your details on the sign
up section
of our website a member of the team will be contacting you within one to two
days to get
you started with the sign up process. The next step is to make the profile but
don't
worry we will do this for you. Our team will make you a fully verified profile
and once
this is complete you are ready for the next steps. At this stage you are going
to be assigned a mentor
she is there to guide you through your whole webcam journey. She is going to
teach you
absolutely everything that you need to know and support you along the way. Our
mentors are truly
a tribute to the company and you'll be in very safe hands as we have a combined
experience
of over 20 years in the coming industry. I have personally hand-selected my
mentors
and I've worked with them for several years so I am confident they will give
you the best possible
service. As well as the ongoing support from your mentor you will also be
invited to join our
exclusive WhatsApp group where you'll receive support from myself, the other
mentors and the
other webcam girls. This chat is the perfect place to ask for advice, share
your own advice or even
share a funny calm story because trust me you'll have a few. We want you to be
the very best you
can be. This is why we've created a free members area on our website where you
can access articles,
training, events, competitions and the members forum. We are continuously
adding to our growing
training and article library as we feel it's very important to always expand
your knowledge.
In our events section you'll be able to find our upcoming in-person and virtual
events.
Our online events are hosted by the Zoom call and they include training from
experts in our industry
and in different industries. We regularly host social catch-ups, work our calls
and meditation
calls. We even deliver a mental health workshop and check-in every month with
our in-house therapist
as we believe looking after your mental health is just as important as looking
after your physical
health. We also offer photoshoot to our members. You will feel so empowered and
so confident after
the shoot when you see how beautiful the photos turn out. Here you'll get to
meet the other girls
and enjoy your fun day over all. After the shoot we will send you the photos
and you can upload
these to your profile and even sell them on your profile and make money while
you sleep. Everyone's
calm experience is unique but what we all share is the right of fair treatment,
access to information
and support and knowledge about our rights. We are committed to empowering you
to be the best
version of you. Calm can be an incredible way to explore your sexuality and
gain confidence.
You'll be surprised how much you can change your life. Join us and positively
impact your mental,
physical and spiritual health. Thank you for watching and I hope to speak to
you soon.